<?xml version="1.0"?>
<catalogue>
	<product code="QB-1223-AA">
		<productName>Router Biscuit Joint</productName>
		<description>By using this tungsten carbide tipped cutter in your router you can join corners, edge to surface, and edge to edge, without the cost of a specialist machine. Each cutter has a bearing to set the correct depth for the biscuit being used. Each cutter has a bearing to set the correct depth for the type of biscuit being used, overall cutter diameter 41mm, cutting dimensions are:- No 20 Cutter 1/4&quot; Shank - Width of cut 4mm/Depth of cut 14mm. No 10 Cutter 1/4&quot; Shank - Width of cut 4mm/Depth of cut 11mm. Follow your machine&apos;s instructions to ensure safe operation. The Beechwood flat dowels are pressed for high tensile strength. Incredibly strong way to join man-made board and solid wood.</description>
		<price>8.5</price>
		<manufacturer>Makita</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1223-AB">
		<productName>Router Cutter Set</productName>
		<description>Professional router sets. All bits feature high quality carbide tips. Each one is ground and balanced to eliminate excessive vibration and ensure a chatter free cut. Bearings are fitted where necessary to prevent burn marks. Follow your machine&apos;s instructions to ensure safe operation.</description>
		<price>25</price>
		<manufacturer>Bosch</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1224-AA">
		<productName>Industrial Circular Saw Blade</productName>
		<description>One of the world&apos;s largest manufacturers of saw blades, Freud products are packed with innovative design features to ensure long life and safe operation. With quality control second to none, they are the out and out first choice for the professional tradesman.</description>
		<price>5</price>
		<manufacturer>Krupps</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1225-AA">
		<productName>Shelving System</productName>
		<description>Fully adjustable twin-slot shelving system from one of the world&apos;s largest manufacturers of shelving. Made of thick gauge steel and finished with a tough, epoxy coating to withstand knocks and discolouration. Used for offices, libraries, commercial, domestic, schools, shops and showrooms. Safety tested and approved by SGS UK.</description>
		<price>25</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AA">
		<productName>Floodlight Camera PIR</productName>
		<description>Easy to install surveillance system using your own TV and VCR. Provides 24 hour surveilance from high resolution, weatherproof black and white camera. PIR activates light at night, sound audio alert at all times. Can be set to auto record all activations. Kit contains: Flood light, PIR camera, 12V transformer, 20m cable, scart lead, control module, auto record controller, 100W halogen bulb and batteries.</description>
		<price>40</price>
		<manufacturer>Makita</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AB">
		<productName>Professional Floodlights</productName>
		<description>PIR floodlights that are designed for professional installation. A faulty light requiring a return visit will cost far more than a quality light does in the first place. 3 year guarantee.</description>
		<price>120</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AC">
		<productName>Tungsten Halogen Lamp</productName>
		<description>Tungsten Halogon Lamps provide an excellent quality of light. Install using a cloth to avoid fingerprints reducing life.</description>
		<price>23</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AD">
		<productName>Low Energy Bulb</productName>
		<description>Use 80% less energy than standard bulbs. -Fits standard fitting. -Last at least 8 times longer than standard bulbs.</description>
		<price>2</price>
		<manufacturer>Bosch</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AE">
		<productName>Low Voltage Halogen Lighting</productName>
		<description>Ideal for restricted ceiling spaces and where a clear, white light is required. Uses approximately 60% less energy. Very easy to fit. All wiring can be completed externally then pushed inside the ceiling void through the downlight hole. Use transformer that matches bulb wattage.</description>
		<price>5</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AF">
		<productName>Low Voltage Halogen Downlighter</productName>
		<description>Suitable for general, accent and display lighting where a clear white light is required. Uses approx. 60% less energy. Easy to install. Use a transformer that matches the lamp wattage.</description>
		<price>6</price>
		<manufacturer>Bosch</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1226-AG">
		<productName>Mains Voltage Halogen Lighting</productName>
		<description>Mains voltage halogen lighting. Now there is no need to use a transformer for halogen lights. Save money and fitting time. As easy to fit as a mains downlight, looks exactly the same as a low voltage light. Fully dimmable.</description>
		<price>8</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1227-AA">
		<productName>Pegler Brassware</productName>
		<description>Pegler are a British Gas Company with a worldwide reputation for quality. All Pegler products are manufactured to the highest standards, guaranteeing a long working life.</description>
		<price>2</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1227-AB">
		<productName>Copper Push Fit</productName>
		<description>Cuprofit is a new range of quality push fit copper fittings from the makers of Conex. WRAS approved system, provides long-lasting, safe and secure joints without the need for flames or flux on site. -Suitable for drinking water and hot or cold water, including central heating. -Use with copper or plastic pipe -WRAS, DVGW and KIWA approved. -Tamper resistant, but demountable. Specification: Suitable for copper tube to EN1057:1996. Suitable for PEX and PB pipe, with appropriate pipe liner. Maximum working pressure 16 bar. Connection can be rotated 360 degrees + or - 2 degree angularity.</description>
		<price>1</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1227-AC">
		<productName>Underground Drainage</productName>
		<description>A top quality range of PVC-u underground pipe and fittings in golden brown (unless indicated) to BS 4660/BSEN 1401-1-1998. Suitable for gravity drainage and sewerage installations at depths of up to 10 metres. Ring seal joints act as both a sealing and expansion joint. Access chamber/inspection chamber and accessories are to BS EN124.</description>
		<price>13</price>
		<manufacturer>Makita</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1227-AD">
		<productName>Push Fit Fittings</productName>
		<description>For hot and cold plumbing and central heating including pressurised and combi systems. Pushes straight onto copper tube, use pipe inserts for plastic pipe. Water Research Council approved. Removable and re-usable. British Gas Service approved for water pipes. No tools needed. BS 7291 PT1 Class S. Use 350mm copper pipe when coupling to a boiler.</description>
		<price>1.5</price>
		<manufacturer>Makita</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1227-AE">
		<productName>Chrome Compression Fitting</productName>
		<description>High quality chrome plate on brass fittings made to BS864 part 2.</description>
		<price>5.99</price>
		<manufacturer>Bosch</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1228-AA">
		<productName>Tool Pouche and Bag</productName>
		<description>Made using only the best materials. Will give any tradesman many years of reliable service</description>
		<price>7</price>
		<manufacturer>Makita</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1229-AA">
		<productName>9.4KG Workbench</productName>
		<description>Just 9.4kg makes this tough workbench ideal for site work. Working size 820 x 605 x 650mm, fold flat storage size 950 x 605 x 180mm. Asymmetric vice action 0-110mm. Integral tool rack. Requires assembly. Maximum load 100kg.</description>
		<price>70</price>
		<manufacturer>Bosch</manufacturer>
	</product>

	<product code="QB-1229-AB">
		<productName>Mastercut 1000 Workbench</productName>
		<description>The perfect combination of workbench and machine table. Suitable for all jigsaws and circular handsaws with a depth of cut of up to 66mm. -Long adjustable guide for precise cuts -Fold-out panel for long workpieces -Angle guide can be set to any angle +/- 60 -Complete with split insert, push stick, switch clamp, safety switch and integrated vice. Specification: Working height 865mm. Total work surface 855 x 540mm. MDF work surface 455 x 540mm. Weight 31kg. 5 year guarantee.</description>
		<price>99</price>
		<manufacturer>Black and Decker</manufacturer>
	</product>
</catalogue>